

My Contact

- +49 17670040723
- 40599 Dusseldorf, Germany
- ww.github.com/sima1358
- in www.linkedin.com/in/simafshar1979

Skill

- HTML5 & CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- · Bootstrap framework
- SASS
- Node and NPM
- React
- DOM Manipulation
- HTTP Requests
- REST API Development with Express
- Database fundamentals with MongoDB
- Security and authentication
- Linux, Git and GitHub
- Microsoft Office

Language

- Persian (Native)
- English (C1)
- Italian (B2)
- German (B1)

Education Background

- DCI Digital Career Institute GmbH, Berlin Certificate
 Completed in August 2023
- Azad University, Iran Bachelor's degree Completed in June 2002

Hobby

- Coding
- Driving
- Sport

SIMA AFSHAR

Fullstack Web Developer

About Me

I am a full-hearted Fullstack Web Developer with a sincere commitment to continuous learning and a deep passion for frontend and backend development. My unwavering commitment to excel in these areas inspires my inner drive, and I hold a deep appreciation for collaborative teamwork, where I can actively lend my skills and expertise to create solutions which has been revised.

Professional Experience

- Hermes (Germany) | Data Entry Operator 11.2021- 03.2022
 - · Key responsibilities:
 - Conducted precise information entry, prioritizing accuracy.
 - Ensured cargo integrity by examining broken packages.
 - Managed checklists to track and validate shipments.
 - · Upheld Hermes's shipping quality and reliability
- Amazon (Germany) | Warehouse Operator 10.2020- 10.2021
 - Key responsibilities:
 - Excelled in tracking applications for timely and correct Amazon deliveries.
 - Showcased sturdy organizational capabilities for green bundle handling.
 - · Prioritized customer satisfaction by using exceeding delivery objectives.
- Amazon (Italy) | Warehouse Operator 01.2019- 05.2020
 - Key responsibilities:
 - · Significantly aided Amazon warehouse operations.
 - Efficiently scanned and tracked items for accurate inventory.
 - · Optimized item placement, enhancing accessibility.
 - Boosted ordinary warehouse performance.
- Antovenetta Bank (Italy) | Data Entry Operator 11.2018- 12.2018
 - Key responsibilities:
 - Ensured data integrity with meticulous approach.
 - Supported operational techniques through specific report preserving.
 - Proficient in Excel for powerful information enter and control.

Projects

1. https://github.com/sima1358/portfolio

- Very simple website which is created by HTML & CSS are used in this project as a very simple portfolio
- The main goal was using animation and transition

2. https://github.com/sima1358/eccomobilien

- An property website to help users to rent or sale different properties by HTML, CSS and JavaScript are used
- The main goal was using data folder as a database

3. https://github.com/sima1358/Ecco-Travel

- Developed a travel website to find economic travel packages by using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- The main goal was using different components and video as a background

4. https://github.com/sima1358/simple-login

 A very simple login page to utilize MongoDB as the backend database while ensuring a secure login page implementation with authentication and password configuration.

5.https://github.com/GroceryGuruGroup/GroceryGuru

 An online supermarket professional website which is created by JavaScript; a remote and teamwork project